Contact

dmpoteet@att.net

www.linkedin.com/in/shon-poteet-r-n-62377a82 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Word Customer Service

Shon Poteet, R.N.

Obstetric Home Health Registered Nurse at Option Care Health Cypress, Texas

Summary

A hard working, highly organized Registered Nurse with over five years of experience in Women's Services, seeking a position as an Obstetric Home Health/Injection Nurse. Ideally, this position would allow for focus on a high level of compassionate, professional, patient-centered care, while maintaining personal and professional growth.

Experience

Option Care Health
Obstetric Home Health Registered Nurse
March 2020 - Present (3 months)

CHI St. Luke's Health
Labor and Delivery Nurse
February 2017 - March 2020 (3 years 2 months)

Cypress Fairbanks Medical Center Hospital Labor & Delivery Nurse July 2014 - February 2017 (2 years 8 months)

Pro Aire Aerial Photography Office Manager July 2007 - June 2010 (3 years) Spring, tx.

Duties included reconciling accounts payable/accounts receivable, compiled client portfolios, and streamlined advertising efforts

Education

Lone Star College System – Cy-Fair Associates Degree of Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2014)